bvp.com 2016-12-05

# Privacy Policy | Bessemer Venture Partners

Bessemer Venture Partners knows your privacy is important to you, it is important to us too.  This Privacy Policy explains the types of information we collect through [www.bvp.com](http://www.bvp.com/) (the “Site”), how we will use it, and how we plan to protect such information once it is collected.  Please review this Policy to make sure you understand how any personal information you provide us will be handled.

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time.  When we do, we will let you know by posting the changed [Privacy Policy on this page](http://www.bvp.com/privacy-policy).  In some cases, for example, if we make any significant changes, we may contact you directly about them, such as by sending you an e-mail.  Any changes will be effective immediately upon posting to the Site.

### What information do we collect on the Site?

We collect two general types of information from Site users:  (1) non-personal information concerning the use of the Site and (2) personal information that identifies or can be used to identify or contact an individual.

·  _Non-Personal Information:_ As is the case with many Web sites, our servers automatically collect your browser type and IP address when you visit the Site.  In addition, we may use standard tracking technologies (e.g., cookies, local shared objects, and pixel tags) and website analytics tools to monitor and better understand user behavior on the Site.  Data captured may include, for example, the referring page that linked you to the Site, the country from which you are conducting your browsing session, the next Web site you visit when you leave the Site, and any search terms you have entered on the Site or a referral site. Such data does not identify you personally. 

·  _Personal Information:_   The personal information we collect is limited to information you submit to us.  For example, we may collect your e-mail address or other information you provide when you contact us through the Site.  We may also collect names, home addresses, or other types of personal information from our investors and business partners to help verify that they are authorized to access the pages of our website dedicated to them, if any such pages exist.

### **How do we use your information?**

We consider the personal information that we receive to be confidential.  We will not use your personal information without your consent, except in accordance with this policy.  If you submit your e-mail address or other personal information to us via the Site, we will use this information only to the extent necessary to respond to your request(s). 

We use the non-personal information collected about Site visits, including the pages you view, information you search for, and the average time spent on our Site, in the aggregate to better understand our audience and increase the functionality and user-friendliness of our Site.  Aggregate information is anonymous.

### **Sharing with Third Parties**

We generally do not share personal information collected through the Site.  We may, however, share your personal information (i) with trusted third parties who provide services to us, (ii) as required by law and when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights or those of third parties, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or comply with a court order or other legal process, or (iii) in connection with a corporate change including a merger, acquisition or sale of assets. 

In addition, the third parties that support our website analytics tools may be able to view aggregate Site usage information that we obtain. 

### **Security**

While we endeavor to protect the security and integrity of Personal Information in our care, due to the inherent nature of the Internet as an open global communications vehicle, we cannot guarantee that any information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our system or otherwise in our care, will be absolutely safe from intrusion by others, such as hackers.

### **Links to Third-Party Web Sites**

Our Site may contain links, banners, widgets or advertisements that lead to other Web sites, including personal blogs written or edited by members of our staff.  We are not responsible for these other sites, and so their privacy policies (not this Policy) will govern the collection and use of your information on them.  We encourage you to read the privacy statements of such Web sites to understand how your information is treated.

### **Consent to Processing**

Our Site and this Privacy Policy are intended to comply with U.S. law.  By providing personal information on the Site, you consent to the transmission and collection and processing of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and U.S. law.

### **Contact Us**

We welcome your questions and comments about privacy.  Please feel free to contact us by sending an e-mail to _[privacy@bvp.com](mailto:privacy@bvp.com)_.
